We are here at the Osamu Tezuka Blackjack Store!
Mr. Mae attended the event and came to the opening ceremony yesterday, and in honor of that, I asked him to come with me today!
When we were little, in the second or third grade, Black Jack started at 7:00 p.m.
You and Mei-chan remembered the airing time?
Isn't that amazing? I remember it was on Sunday at 7:00 p.m. on Nittele.
Wasn't it on Sunday? It's like...
So the anime was on weekdays at 7:00 p.m.?
That's amazing.
This time, I'm visiting the cartoon side.
I'd like to take a look at it right away.
I'm going to ask you to show me around.
I'll be going.
Yes, so there are four rooms in this exhibition.
Yes, I heard that there is a fourth room.
The sun is shining so brightly, isn't it?
The weather is so nice.
I can't open my eyes at all.
It's so bright.
So, this is the first room.
The blackjack shifts.
I'll give you the main sheet for each of them.
Do you have a favorite character, Misato?
What? Misato...
Misato, the original Misato, is pretty...
She's got this cute visual.
Her monologue is amazing.
Oh, really? Oh, yeah?
Covered in pretty leather.
Like a wolf.
Like a bunch of greed.
So much greed.
I'm remembering how excited I was when I was still here.
You remember?
I thought I understood it, but it's like...
I don't know, morality.
And I think I know both sides of people.
I think I know both sides of people.
And also, I wonder if it's a way of looking at life and death.
I think I can learn something about the thirst for life.
I think I can learn something like that.
Yes, that's right.
Now, let's come to the second room.
You can't really start from here, can you?
From here, ordinary people can do it.
Ordinary people can.
I'll make a special exception.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to show you some of them.
In the second room...
It's Black Jack's birthday celebration.
Mr. Sasaki's masterpieces are on display.
Mr. Sasaki's masterpieces...
Yes, that's right. Yeah.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I've learned from the past that your work has been serialized in this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a great feeling.
Black Jack is like...
You can learn about diseases that you didn't know you had.
You can learn about things you didn't know.
That's true.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Last year, I had a surgery to terminate my bio-principle.
You know, the surgery I had last year?
You know...
I heard that your character had the same surgery.
I get it. I get it.
It saves me a little, right?
It saves me a little.
I wish I had a Dr. Black Jack around me.
I'm sure he'd fix you up in no time.
He charges me for music, though.
That's true.
Hey...
I have all the original drawings from the first episode.
It's amazing.
I'd really like you to see it.
So that's it?
I wrote the text first, and then I retyped it in patch form.
This is what the cartoonist wrote for the uniforms and so on. The cartoonist writes this on the uniform or something like that.
The editor pastes it neatly on the page.
But nowadays, you know, we're in the digital age, you know.
But nowadays, you know, we're in the digital age.
A handwritten manuscript is a raw manuscript.
With a correction pen like this.
With correction pens.
Or white ones...
You don't see that now, do you?
The fine touch of the pen.
I've already started looking at this.
I could spend three hours just looking at this.
The way the color was applied.
Digital is so different from now.
I'm worried.
I wonder if there are any books.
Human skin is amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's really beautiful.
Oh, this is a little bit of this shading.
It's like shoes.
Yeah, it's like, I painted it brown first.
I painted it with a brown window or an S-shape.
And then I colored in the paperback, and then I added the shoe-like shading to it.
I wonder how long that took.
It's true.
Then the third quality Then the third quality
Let me tell you guys, this.
Mandalan, mandalan, mandalan.
I think it's going to be two pieces.
It's a room arranged by serial editions.
Mandalan.
First time I said it, Mandalan.
When I see Tomoyozuku, I really cry.
I really cry, I really cry.
In the anime, you know, in the latter half of the movie
You know how the skin is like this?
When I did the transplant surgery...
The story of the boy who gave me the skin
It's about Black Jack.
This is how Black Jack grew up.
The story of how Black Jack grew up is told in each chapter and each series.
Please take a good look at them!
Mr. Staff
You've become a staff member, staff member.
I'm sure you'll feel more deeply and have more feelings if you see it now.
Maybe so, because we were kids.
I thought the characters were cute or cool or funny or scary.
or funny or scary.
I only remembered them as cute, cool, funny, scary, etc.
But now we can learn more about ourselves.
It's amazing, it's a story about a boy who plays baseball.
I can't believe you really cut out the real newspapers!
It's true.Oh, my God.
That's great.
That's great. I didn't know that. Isn't it amazing? That's how real things are made.
Wow, now we have a whole theme.
I see. This is the section where the works are displayed separately.
Was the surgery a success? But what happened after? Something like that.
One of my favorite parts of Black Jack is the gag scene with animals.
Speaking of gags, there are a lot of scenes where the characters are gagging, like in "Achon Prikke".
But when the story is serious and there is a surgical scene, and animals are in it, it's always a bit sad.
It makes me sad, but one of my favorites is a gag panel with a bear in it, which I didn't expect to see in a gag panel.
I was like, "Oh, this is a gag panel." It's sad, isn't it?
It's a sad story about brothers... brothers, or rather, a bear and a man fighting.
It's a story about a nemesis, a bear named Jinbeh, who was a nemesis of mine, and my sister is involved.
And my sister is related to it.
It's a little bit more exciting to see this, raw silver.
It's written with a magic marker.
Magic pen? It's like a watercolor pen or something like that.
You can stick all kinds of pens on it.
Blackjack is a lot of work.
First of all, it's black.
Yes, yes, because it's black.
Once, it looks like blackjack.
A duplicate.
I mean, there was a circle...
There was a circle.
There was a circle with a guy who looked like Black Jack.
Black Jack by mistake.
I painted over the whole thing. It's all painted over.
In the comics.
I made a mistake here.
After that, Suzuki Sensei...
"Mr. Suzuki made a mistake in one of the panels.
There's also a part where it appears.
It must have been a pain in the ass.
Correcting it.
The images kept playing on the rate screen.
Animation.
Animated images.
And that's the one with the Western-style clothes.
Black Jack.
Surgery.
When he was little.
Is this the first episode?
It's full of pinocchios.
Pinocchio-themed.
A lot of pinocchios.
I want to see it seriously, don't you? That's right.
I want to see it.
I saw a lot of things yesterday.
I'm talking to you a lot.
I want to see.
I feel like I want to see it.
Hey.
In cartoons,In animation,
See, it's about 24 minutes.
Anime is a 30-minute cartoon, so it's usually...
So, I had to stretch it out to 24 minutes,
So, various scenes are slightly different from the original work,
And then, there are some scenes that are different from the original work.
The ending is the same, but the story is the same.
The ending is the same.
But the ending is the same.
Look at this.
Yes. I would like you to look for them, and I would like you to look at the manga again.
Lastly, I would like to introduce the fourth theory, "Left Se.
This one is about medicine and art,
Or, medical care and modernity,
It seems to be exhibited according to themes related to medicine.
It's a hospital, isn't it? It's a hospital.
Sensei, Sensei, Sensei,
The true meaning of medicine.
That's right.
Really.
I wonder how much he studied.
I wonder how much he learned about infectious diseases that cause the body to shrink,
I see it now, like an unidentifiable infectious disease,
We were in a panic over coronas until recently, weren't we?
What? Isn't this a recent phenomenon? I think it's just a recent thing.
That is one of the reasons.
In this exhibition, real news from the Showa period is also displayed.
I wonder if they really thought about that?I wonder if that kind of thing was really thought out?
When you get to the fourth room, there are displays all over the wall, it's amazing.
You can look for your favorite scene, this story, this story, this story.
It's amazing.
That's what this is all about. It was an earthquake.
It's a great scene.
What is the Showa for?
It's shrinking.
Yes.
And quotes, you know, there are a lot of them.
Quotes, you can look for your favorite quotes.
I really don't have enough time.
It's not enough.
Not enough time.
There's so much on display that it's not even necessary to have so much. There are so many exhibits.
There are so many exhibits.
I would like you to take a look at them.
Please go and take a look.
Wow!
So cute!
So I'm a pinocchio too?
Looking at all the pinocchios...
I'm a pinocchio too?
I wanted to do it, but I couldn't.
I made a mistake.
You're like an uncle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're all so good. You're all so good.
You're good at looking at faces.
I'm in front of Mr. Pinoke right now.
There's a man who can smile like this.
In front of you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yes, there was.
Not a bad match.
Which Pinocchio do you like?
Do you like it?
Yes, and
At Black Justin.
You can also buy
Very cute!
The exhibition's original
Martial arts uniforms are also available.
very fashionable and cute.
We have a lot of cute ones.
Isn't the gold kimono cute?
I bought this one.
It's so cute!
They're also putting a lot of effort into T-shirts.
Aren't they cute? Like this one.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The slim shells in the middle.
Pinocchio here is cute too!
Isn't he cute?Hey, isn't she cute?
Pinocchio with various expressions.
They're so cute!
Which one is your favorite?
This one.
This one?
I like this one.
Is he mad?
Little Pinocchio.
He's adorable.
I can't decide.
I can't decide what to eat.
Black curry.
Because there's a curry scene or something.
Coffee and Curry
Coffee and curry.
There's also coffee.
And also
I recommend it.
Blood transfusion style
blood transfusion jelly
Strawberry flavor.
I've never seen it.
It's like this...
A pure and honest world line
And all kinds of goods
Goods that mesh with each other.The goods you're engaging with.
I can feel the love.
I can't get lost in this one.
Yes, and now we're wearing
It's a collaboration with Mr. Glam!
So cute!
So stylish!
Strawberries are cute too!
Leather jacket
It has a print on the back.
It's on the inside.
Isn't it amazing inside?
It's amazing.
The lining is so cute.
It's so detailed.
It's amazing.
The lining is so cute.
Have you ever seen such stylish anime goods?
I can wear this every day.
I can wear it every day.
It's really cute!
Get it!
Then you can enjoy the after-nutty of mushrooms!